本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 林 易如反掌 小坏玩意儿 老虎娘 Echo 兰丰
校对： 爽爷  后期： mask
美国舰队基地 昆迪克
海军罪案调查处 第十一季 第八集
NCIS S11E08
"犯罪现场"
"Alibi"
达克 我这边结束了
All right, Ducky, I'm done.
谢谢 蒂姆
Thank you, Tim.
可怜的小东西
You poor dear.
戴着耳机都没有听到车开过来吧
Probably didn't even hear it coming.
托尼在哪里呢?
Hey, where's Tony?
我不知道
I don't know.
我本来说要载他一程
I offered to give him a lift,
但是他说有人会去接他
but he said someone would pick him up.
从哥伦比亚特区开到昆迪克吗?
From DC to Quantico?
我也觉得很奇怪
Sounded strange to me, too.
没有车真不知道他是怎么活的
I don't know how he's surviving without a car.
是他吗?
Is that him?
不 是黛利拉
No. It's Delilah.
我们正计划溜出去度过一个漫长周末呢
We're talking about sneaking away for a long weekend.
真有你的
Nice.
你们要是墨迹完了
If you hens are finished,
就过来帮忙
I could do with some help.
好的
Oh, yes.
她的身份是下士乔迪・雷
Her name's Petty Officer Third Class Jody Ray.
巡逻队日出时分发现了她的尸体
Patrol spotted her body just after sunrise.
她在基地诊所工作
She works at the base clinic.
昨晚九点打卡下班
Punched out just after 2100 last night.
然后就出来跑步了吗?
And she went for a run?
同事说她正在进行马拉松训练
Coworker said she was training for a marathon.
几个月来几乎每晚都在跑步
Had been running almost every night for the past few months.
通知亲属了吗?
Next of kin been notified?
伤亡援助电话处的人正在通知 长官
CACO team is on it, sir.
知道了 谢谢
All right, thanks.
很高兴看到你来了 迪诺左
Nice of you to join us, DiNozzo.
抱歉迟到了
Yeah, sorry.
嘿 吉米
Hey, Jimmy.
我错过什么没有?
So, what did I miss?
是谁大老远开车送你过来的?
Who was it that drove you all the way over here?
一个朋友
A friend.
别打马虎眼
No, seriously.
真的只是一个朋友
Seriously.
我有什么工作 拍照吗?
What should I do, photograph?
不用 我已经做完了
No, I already did it.
好吧
gh. All right.
达克?
Duck?
死亡时间 昨天晚上十点左右
Last night, 2200 hours,or thereabouts.
嘿 艾比
Hey, Abbs.
有什么发现吗?
Come up with anything?
有点进展
Making progress.
你看 这块碎片是车头灯零件的一部分
Look, okay, this is a part of the vehicle's headlight assembly.
厂商和型号?
What's the make and model?
全国有四十七家汽车生产商
There are 47 manufacturers of cars and trucks in the United States.
每一家都有好多型号和风格
Each one of those produces multiple models and body styles.
配件和车饰每隔几年就会推陈出新
And the parts and the trim are redesigned every few years.
有无数种可能性呢
There are zillions of possibilities.
为什么每个人都认为
Why would anyone assume that I could take
通过一块小小的塑料
a teeny, tiny piece of plastic
我就能轻松地辨别出车型呢?
and easily identify a vehicle?
厂商和型号?
What's the make and model?
是一辆零三至零五年生产的
A 2003 to a 2005
道奇公羊敞篷小卡车
Dodge Ram pickup truck.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
但是还是得缩小范围才行
But we're going to have to narrow it down.
基地里面每天都有上百辆卡车来来回回
There's hundreds of trucks on that base every day.
我正打算这么做呢 你就来打断我了
That's what I was doing when you interrupted me.
下士雷的手表上面蹭上了
So, there was a trace of the vehicle's paint
肇事车辆的一点油漆
on Petty Officer Ray's watch.
可能是这两种颜色
These are our color choices.
上面的是烈焰红
On the top we have Inferno Red.
下面的是深熔融红
And the bottom we have Deep Molten Red.
真不知道是谁想出这些名字的
I don't know who comes up with these names.
你认为呢?
What do you think?
我觉得上面的比较符合
I'm going to have to go with the top one.
我也这么认为
Agreed.
烈焰红只有零五至零八年有生产
So Inferno Red was only available between 2005 and 2008.
所以结合车灯和颜色
So the only year in common
唯一符合的年份就是零五年
between the headlight lens and the color is 2005.
因此 我们要找的是一辆
Ergo we are looking for
零五年产的红色道奇公羊敞篷小卡车
a red 2005 Dodge Ram pickup truck.
艾比 你是最棒的
Abby, you are the best.
你还是想当然
Still taken for granted.
听起来很简单 实际很难的
Just 'cause I make it look easy doesn't mean it is.
为什么认为
Why do you suspect
上士贾斯汀・邓恩有嫌疑?
Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne?
艾比根据厂商 型号 颜色
Abby I.D.'d the make, model and color
定位了肇事逃逸的卡车
of the hit-and-run vehicle.
基地里面只有一辆卡车符合条件 车主是邓恩
Only one registered on base and it belongs to Dunne.
我检查了大门的安检录像
I checked the gate security footage.
他的车昨天晚上没有离开过昆迪克
His truck never left Quantico last night.
- 他的个人情况? - 单身
- What do we know about him? - Single.
高中毕业就参军
Joined the Corps right out of high school.
是一名直升机修理工
He's a helo mechanic.
原定本周末参加地中海两栖登陆
Scheduled to deploy on an LHA to the Med, later this week.
最可疑的是...
And most pertinent...
他有醉酒驾车的记录
he has a DUI in his past.
把他带过来
Bring him in.
我好喜欢案件进展神速
I love it when it all comes together so quickly.
我可不是 弄得我很紧张
Not me. Makes me nervous.
有点过于容易
Too easy.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你打算永远都不买新车了吗?
You ever going to get a new car?
首先 我从来没有买过新车
Well, firstly, I never buy new cars.
其次 我需要的是能够点燃我热情的东西
Secondly, I need something that ignites my passions.
这就跟女人一样
It's like a woman.
在许下承诺之前总要先坠入爱河吧
I need to be in love before I commit.
这么说你从来没有跟女人许诺过了
You've never committed to a woman.
军士邓恩 我们是海军罪案调查处
Sergeant Dunne. NCIS.
军士邓恩!
Sergeant Dunne!
不许动 海军罪案调查处
Freeze. NCIS.
没错 这是我的车 但是
Yeah, that's my truck, but
我发誓不知道它怎么成这样子了
I swear, I don't know how it got that way.
- 你昨天晚上没有开吗? - 没有
- You didn't drive it last night? - No.
我好几天没开车了
I haven't used the truck in a couple of days.
那你怎么上班?
How do you get to work?
走路 可以锻炼身体
I walk. Need the exercise.
维修站离我的住处没多远
The maintenance bay isn't that far from my quarters.
昨天晚上十点你在哪里?
Where were you last night, 2200 hours?
在我房间里面... 睡觉
I was in my room... asleep.
这周很难熬
Had a tough week.
简直是筋疲力尽
I was exhausted.
你确定昨天晚上自己没有喝醉
You sure you weren't drunk
然后把自己做过什么都忘得一干二净?
and you just don't remember what you did?
我们知道你曾经醉酒驾车
We know about your DUI.
我已经十三个月滴酒不沾了
I've been sober for 13 months.
我每周都要去互助会三四次
I go to three or four meetings a week.
如果你是无辜的 昨天晚上没有开车
So, if you weren't driving the pickup and you're innocent,
为什么要跳窗逃跑?
why were you climbing out a window?
我知道自己的基本权利
I know my rights.
见到律师之前 我不会再说一个字
I'm not saying any more until I have a lawyer.
好的
Okay.
你可以叫自己的律师
Then you can have the lawyer of your choice
或者法官为你指定一位
or JAG will assign one to you.
嘿 麦基
Hey, McGee.
军士邓恩的右脚靴子带来了吗?
Did you bring me Sergeant Dunne's right boot?
抱歉 艾比 他走律师程序了
Sorry, Abbs, he lawyered up
不允许我们搜查
and didn't give a permissive search.
那你有仔细看他的脚吗?
Hmm. Well, did you get a good look at his feet?
什么?
Huh?
你在现场做的脚印模型
Well, the footprint that you cast at the crime scene,
是标准的海军陆战队战斗靴
it's a standard-issue Marine Corps combat boot,
十号半
size ten and a half.
我猜他可能穿这个号码
Well, I guess he might wear that size.
鞋子磨损得很厉害
It's well worn
并在右跟处有独特的裂缝
and has a very distinctive gash in the right heel.
我真的很想跟军士邓恩比对一下
I'd just really love to match it to Sergeant Dunne.
那得等到明天早上了
Well, you're going to have to wait till morning.
这里有什么发现吗?
Any luck here?
这就是我们要找的卡车
Oh, this is definitely the pickup truck.
轮胎跟现场泥中的车轮印吻合
The tires match the tracks that were in the dirt.
车辆前端找到的头发 血渍 衣物纤维
And I got hair, blood and clothing fibers
也跟受害者吻合
off the front end that match our victim.
早上就能拿到DNA结果
So, I'll get DNA confirmation in the morning,
那就铁证如山了
and we should have it locked up.
太好了
Great.
嘿 自从托尼车子坏掉以后
Hey, have you been giving Tony rides to work
你有接他上班吗?
since his car was wrecked?
没有
No.
今天早上有人
Somebody dropped him off
大老远送他到昆迪克
all the way out at Quantico this morning.
他是不是在和谁约会?
Is he dating someone?
哦... 我可不这么认为
Oh... I don't think so.
哼
Hmm.
你闻起来总是那么迷人
You always smell so great.
让我猜猜 你今年肯定又错过
Let me guess, you missed the sexual harassment meeting
性骚扰大会
again this year.
嘿 大伙 看我在大厅里面发现了谁
Hey, everybody, look who I found in the lobby.
嘿 克拉克
Hey, Clark.
- 嘿 伙计们 - 早上好 凯莉
- Hey, guys. - Morning, Carrie.
真不敢相信我有这个荣幸
I don't think I've had the pleasure.
马拉德医生
Dr. Mallard,
这位是联邦调查局前任探员凯莉・克拉克
meet former FBI agent Carrie Clark.
现在从事个人律师业务
Now in private law practice.
很高兴见到你 医生
Nice to meet you, Doctor.
- 我也是 - 凯莉几年前
- Likewise. - Carrie worked
负责诺福克郡那边港务局的案件
the Norfolk side of the Port Authority case
让福内尔看起来容光焕发了都
a few years ago, made Fornell look good.
磨人的工作
It was a tough job.
不 你们做得更好
No, you guys made it easy.
我不记得那个案件了
I don't remember that case.
达克 重窃罪的案件
Grand theft, Ducky,
啊
Ah.
什么风把你吹来了海军罪案调查处?
What brings you to NCIS?
我来见上士邓恩
I'm here to see Sergeant Dunne.
你是他的代表律师吗?
You're his lawyer?
告诉我们这不是事实
Say it ain't so.
是的 他在哪里?
Yes, where is he?
上士邓恩就在穿过大厅的拘留室内
Staff Sergeant Dunne's in a holding cell across the yard.
探员麦基可以带你去见他
Agent McGee can take you to him.
谢谢
Thank you.
很高兴见到你们
Good to see you guys.
- 再见 - 达克
- Bye. - Duck,
可以随时开始解剖海军士官雷的尸体了
you can release Petty Officer Ray's body any time
你已经准备好
you're ready.
老大 你有没察觉到凯莉有什么不一样吗?
You notice anything different about Carrie, boss?
没有戴着婚戒
No wedding ring.
就告诉过你 丈夫就像是一个手提包
Told you the husband was a handbag.
手提包?
Handbag?
一件挂在你手上但是又无用的东西
Something useless you hang on your arm.
哦
Oh.
嘿 探员福内尔 我是迪诺左
Hey, Agent Fornell, it's DiNozzo.
听好 你能不能给我一些内部消息
Listen, can you give me the skinny
关于迷人的凯莉・克拉克的?
on the ever-fetching Carrie Clark?
你好
Hello.
我是凯莉・克拉克
I'm Carrie Clark.
希望你别中看不中用
Didn't expect you to look like you do.
有什么问题吗?
Is that a problem?
如果你真如我堂弟说的那么厉害的话 没有
Not if you're as good as my cousin said.
好吧 至少我还没有收到过投诉
Well, I haven't had any complaints.
你将会收到几条罪名非常严重的控告
You're about to be arraigned on some very serious charges.
我压根对肇事逃逸这件事情一无所知
I don't know anything about a hit-and-run.
如果真是我的卡车的话 那就是别人开的车
If it was my pickup, someone else was driving.
知道是谁吗?
Any idea who?
贾斯汀 我也想相信你 但是你看起来很紧张
Justin, I want to believe you, but you seem very nervous.
你有没有什么要告诉我?
Is there something that you want to tell me?
昨天晚上十点钟你在哪里?
Where were you at 10:00 last night?
那个无关紧要
Doesn't matter.
这个当然重要
Of course it does.
- 我有不在场证明 - 好吧
- I have an alibi. - Okay.
你应该知道的就只有这些
That's all you need to know.
你打不打算告诉我?
Are you going to tell me?
好吧 如果这就是你的态度
All right, if that is going to be your attitude,
那不妨我帮你省省钱 如何?
how about I save you some money?
军法局会免费帮你安排一位律师
JAG will assign someone to you for free.
等一下
Hold on.
这个房间装有窃听器吗?
Could this room be bugged?
不 不可以 这是不合法的
No, no way, that would be illegal.
你现在有在录下我们的对话吗?
Are you recording our conversation?
没有
No.
你是我的代表律师
You're my lawyer.
我说的任何东西 你都不能告诉任何人吗?
Anything I say, you can't tell anyone?
我们称之为律师-当事人特权
It's called attorney-client privilege.
你所说的都会被保密
Everything that you say is confidential.
所有的信息都不会被带出这间房间 除非你想
It doesn't leave this room unless you want it to.
作为律师的职业道德规则
Rules of ethics prohibit me
也会禁止我向他人透漏我们谈话的内容
from telling anyone what we discuss.
你确定吗?
You sure?
贾斯汀 我向你承诺
I promise you, Justin.
那个女孩被杀的时候
When that girl was killed,
我在三十五英里外的福尔斯彻奇市
I was 35 miles away in Falls Church.
你在那里做什么?
And what were you doing there?
把一个家伙刺死
Stabbing a guy to death.
你为什么要查询航班?
Why are you checking airline schedules?
迈阿密?
Miami?
你是不是非要知道所有事情?
Do you have to know everything?
是的 已经深深融入我的血液
Yes, it's in my DNA.
好吧 如果我不告诉你
Well, you're gonna drive me crazy
你肯定会把我烦疯的 所以...
until I tell you, so...
这里已经没有什么工作
Things are quiet here,
这个案件也将步入结案阶段
this case is wrapping up.
我会有几天假期
I've got a few vacation days coming,
所以黛利拉和我正讨论着
so Delilah and I have been talking
去度一个长周末假
about getting away for a long weekend.
麦基 我对此印象深刻
McGee, I'm impressed.
迈阿密 南海滩 热店 石蟹
Miami, South Beach, hot clubs, stone crabs.
这不像你
It is unlike you.
我就知道我应该闭口不谈的
I knew I shouldn't have said anything.
哦
Oh.
真短时间
That didn't take long.
你的客户终于醒悟过来了?
Your client come to his senses?
- 谢谢你 - 想要供认了吗?
- Thank you. - Wants to confess?
不
No.
那么 是想要庭内和解吗?
Wants to make a deal, then?
上士邓恩说他是无辜的
Sergeant Dunne says he's innocent.
无辜的?
Innocent?
我们已经对比过受害现场的车痕
We've forensically tied his pickup
和他的卡车吻合
to the victim.
当我们想要找他问话的时候 他逃跑了
He ran when we tried to question him.
他声称他有不在场证明
He claims he has an alibi.
好吧 那是什么呢? 我们会去查证
Well, what is it? We'll check it out.
吉布斯 事情没有那么简单
Well, it is not that simple, Gibbs,
这是秘密
he told me in confidence.
当事人特权
It's privileged.
如果他不愿意亲自告诉你
If he doesn't want to tell you himself,
我无能为力
then my hands are tied.
还有四十八小时 要么控告他 要么释放他
We've got 48 hours to either charge him or let him go.
给我们一点线索
Give us something.
好吧 听好 我会自己去查证他的不在场证明
All right, listen, I will go check out his alibi myself
然后我会告知你结果
and I will get back to you.
那个家伙正面临着车祸致死罪
The guy's facing vehicular homicide
还有肇事逃逸罪的控告
and hit-and-run charges.
他还不愿意用不在场证明?
He won't use an alibi?
他是不是疯了?
Is he crazy?
艾比
Abbs.
吉布斯... 你真神奇
Gibbs... you're amazing.
你是怎么知道开车的其实是另有其人?
How did you know that someone else was driving the truck?
你发现了什么?
What'd you find?
这比我什么都没发现还要来得有趣
Well, it's more what I didn't find that's interesting.
我的意思是说 在你打给我之前
I mean, before you called, I was just trying
我只是在尝试把死者受害的信息
to match the victim
和车辆进行比对
to the vehicle, which I did.
- 然后呢? - 然后当你问我
- But? - But then, when you asked me
有没有可能
if there's a chance that someone
开车的另有其人之后
other than the owner of the truck was driving,
我就收集了车上所有的指纹 没有任何发现
I dusted the whole thing for prints, I didn't find any.
- 只有上士邓恩的吗? - 不是
- Just Staff Sergeant Dunne's? - No.
我的意思是 没有任何指纹 什么都没有
I mean, like none, nada, zip, zilch, nothing.
整辆卡车的表面
Almost the entire surface of the truck
几乎都被擦去了指纹...
was wiped clean of fingerprints...
车门把手 方向盘 换挡杆
the door handle, the steering wheel, the gearshift,
座椅调节器 所有的东西
the seat adjuster, everything.
现在 我就想起了我的伯父霍勒斯
Now, I got reminded o-of my Uncle Horace.
他总是忘记东西
He was always losing things
像他的眼镜 钱包 还有钥匙
like his glasses and his wallet and his keys.
很多次都把自己锁在了车里面
He got locked out of his own car so many times
所以他就在自己的车里藏了把钥匙
that he, he hid a key on his car.
然后我就找到了... 这个...
And then I found... this...
...在前轮下面
...under the front wheel well.
也被擦干净了?
Wiped clean?
哦 是的 包括里面的钥匙
Oh, yeah, including the key inside.
这几乎不可能是车主会做的事情
That is hardly something that the owner would do.
开车的另有其人
Someone else was driving the truck.
是的 他们还尽力让它看起来不是那么回事
Yes, and they tried to make it look like they weren't.
谢谢 艾比
Thanks, Abbs.
我不明白为什么人们要跑步健身
I don't understand why people run.
哦 好吧 这是有益健康的
Oh, well, it's therapeutic,
跑步对心血管的健康大有益处
it has great cardiovascular benefits.
而且 可以使得之前的内啡肽发生抽气效应
What's more, it gets the old endorphins pumping.
跟你讲 跑一跑能让我嗨起来
I'll tell you, running gives me a great high.
我指的是司机
I was referring to the driver
肇事逃跑的司机 帕莫先生
running from the scene of the accident, Mr. Palmer.
哦 对的 对的
Oh, yes, yes.
你知道吗 在美国肇事后逃离现场
Did you know that pedestrian hit-and-runs are
发生率非常高?
at an epidemic rate in this country?
将近百分之十一
Nearly 11%
在美国发生的车祸都是
of all traffic accidents in the United States are
肇事逃逸
hit-and-runs.
那位海军士官雷?
That Petty Officer Ray?
是的
Yes.
保留这具尸体再久一点
Hold on to the body for a little while longer,
好吧 达克?
will you, Duck?
你签了释放书
You signed the release.
有什么发生变化吗?
Has something changed?
是的
Yeah.
但是我不知道是什么
But I don't know what.
你好 我是吉布斯
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
我是凯莉・克拉克
Hi, it's Carrie Clark.
哦 凯莉 你有什么发现吗?
Yeah, Carrie, what do you got?
邓恩的不在场证明
Well, Dunne's alibi
查了一下 属实
checks out, it's solid.
- 跟我讲一下 - 我不能
- Mm-hmm, tell me. - I can't.
你要找到真正肇事逃逸的司机
You're going to have to start looking
因为不是我的客户做的
for the real hit-and-run driver because it's not my client.
凯莉 听着 我不能就这样相信你 好吧?
Carrie, look, I can't just take your word for it, okay?
跟我讲点什么
Give me something here.
你要自己查明白 吉布斯
You're gonna have to figure this one out on your own, Gibbs.
杰斯罗 发生什么事情了吗?
Jethro, is something wrong?
似乎今天你要跟我们在一起度过
Looks like you won't be leaving us
亲爱的
today after all, my dear.
麦基
McGee,
追踪一下上一个电话 可以吗?
trace the last call, will you?
你想知道谁打来的吗?
You want me to find out who it was from?
是凯莉・克拉克打来的
It was from Carrie Clark.
通常她的名字会出现在这个小窗口
Usually her name comes up on that little window there.
这次没有出现 只有一个号码
This time it didn't; it was just a number.
她说什么了吗?
What did she say?
说证实了她客户的不在场证明
Said her client's alibi checked out.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
这是一个公用电话的号码
Well, the number belongs to a pay phone.
公用电话?
Pay phone?
我以为现在都没有这东西了
I didn't think there were any left.
福尔斯彻奇市 洋槐路三百二十五号
325 Acacia Avenue in Falls Church.
就在图书馆前面
It's in front of the library.
凯莉有手机
Carrie has a cell.
为什么要用公用电话?
Why would she use a pay phone?
不清楚
Not sure.
她知道客户的不在场证明
She knows her client's alibi.
她知道她不能告诉我们
She knows she can't tell us.
你在想什么 老大?
What are you thinking, boss?
凯莉知道我们会好奇
Carrie knows we'll be intrigued,
她知道我们会追踪这个号码
she knows that we'll trace the call.
她是不是给我们留了一个线索?
Did she just drop a bread crumb?
是的 走吧 出发
Yeah. Go. Go on.
这就是那台公用电话
There's the pay phone.
为什么凯莉在这里打电话?
Why was Carrie calling from here?
图书馆 五金商店?
Library, hardware store?
看 性事良品
Oh, there we go, Great Sexpectations.
我高度怀疑 托尼
I seriously doubt it, Tony.
嘿 有一辆警车
Hey, there's a squad car.
是的 去看看
Yeah, let's check it out.
你发现凯莉离婚了没有?
Did you ever find out if Carrie was divorced?
临时分居
Ah. Trial separation.
她没有戴着戒指
She's not wearing her ring.
那什么意思你懂的
You know what that means.
结束了
It's over.
嘿
Hey.
海军罪案调查处
NCIS.
特别探员迪诺佐和麦基
Special Agents DiNozzo and McGee.
多克里 杀人案
Dockry, Homicide.
杀人案?
Homicide?
你们在忙什么?
What are you guys up to?
哦 就是溜大街 很无聊的海军任务
Oh, just pounding the pavement, boring Navy stuff.
是的 不像杀人案件这么重要的
Yeah, nothing serious like homicide.
谁死了?
Who's dead?
商店主... 唐尼・沙利文
Store owner... Donny Sullivan.
前天晚上被捅死了
Stabbed to death night before last.
员工昨天早上在楼上卧室
Body was found in the upstairs residence
发现了他的尸体
yesterday morning by an employee.
- 线索呢? - 目前还没有
- Any leads? - Nothing concrete yet.
你们有什么需要吗?
Anything I can help you guys with?
不用 我们要走了
Ah, no, we got to go.
他饿了
He gets hungry.
那倒是 回头见
It's true. See you around.
嘿 你们认识一名叫吉布斯的特别探员吗?
Hey, do you guys know a Special Agent Gibbs?
认识 我们亲切地管他叫"老大"
Oh, yeah, we affectionately refer to him as "boss."
告诉他希科里的儿子问好
Tell him Hickory's son said hi.
希科里?
Hickory?
他会知道的
He'll know.
商店主的谋杀案几乎与
The storekeeper's murder happened
肇事逃逸同时发生
about the same time as the hit-and-run.
你觉得这个跟邓恩的不在场证明有关吗?
Think this has something to do with Dunne's alibi?
如果邓恩参与了 那么他是怎么
If Dunne was involved, then how'd he get
从昆迪克到这里来再赶回去的呢?
from Quantico to here and back?
他的卡车没有离开过地下室
His truck never left the base.
我觉得你在迈阿密的热情周末计划
I think your amorous little weekend in Miami
要泡汤了
just went bye-bye.
- 你好 我是吉布斯 - 嘿 老大
- Yeah. Gibbs. - Hey, boss.
有关邓恩的不在场证明我们可能有线索了
We might have a lead on Dunne's alibi.
尽你可能去查... 要小心 迪诺佐
Find out what you can-- discreetly, DiNozzo.
吉布斯 吉布斯 吉布斯 我跟你说过
Gibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs, so I told you that I dusted
我查了整辆卡车 寻找指纹 但是我并没有
the entire truck for prints, but I didn't.
我只是查了一个人会碰到的地方
I only dusted the places that a person would touch,
然后我意识到 如果有人
and then I realized that if someone's going
调整了座位旋转杠杆 并且他们确实调整了
to adjust the seat lever, which they did,
他们可能也会调整一下后视镜
they would probably also adjust the rearview mirror.
猜我找到了什么...
And guess what I found...
背面有一个刚印上去的右拇指指纹
a fresh right thumbprint on its backside.
拇指指纹有名字没有?
Thumbprint have a name?
别傻了 吉布斯
Don't be silly, Gibbs,
拇指指纹没有名字的
thumbprints don't have names.
人才有名字
People do.
我第一步就是将它和
My first pass was to run it
所有在昆迪克的人员进行对比
against all the personnel at Quantico.
而我做到这里就可以了
And that's all I had to do.
二等兵丹尼尔・克里夫
Private Daniel Cliff.
吉布斯很快就过来
Gibbs will be in, in a minute.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道他们为什么把我带过来吗?
You know why they brought me over here?
不知道
No.
我告诉他们 在我的律师到场之前
I told them I wouldn't say anything else
我不会说什么别的了
until my lawyer was present.
我查了你的不在场证明
Well, I checked your alibi.
你没有撒谎
You weren't lying.
嘿 你不知道谁在玻璃另一面
Hey, you don't know who's on the other side of that glass.
我们不要再谈这件事情
Let's not discuss it again.
你知道你要做的是什么
You know all you have to.
我是无辜的
I'm innocent.
这个等不到明天早上吗?
Couldn't this have waited till the morning?
不能
Nope.
- 你认识他吗? - 是的
- You know him? - Yeah,
二等兵克里夫... 我见过他
Private Cliff-- I see him around.
你们俩关系好吗?
You two close?
不
No.
我们以前一起喝过几次酒
We hung a couple of times back when I was drinking.
那是很久之前的事情
That was a long time ago.
最近见过面吗?
Have you seen each other lately?
在洗衣间 娱乐室见过他 就这样
Run into him in the laundry, rec room, that's it.
你允许二等兵克里夫
You give Private Cliff permission
驾驶你的小皮卡了吗?
to drive your pickup truck?
他妈的 才没有
Hell, no.
这是什么事情?
What was that about?
吉布斯? 好像你找到
Gibbs? Sounds like you have
肇事逃逸的嫌疑人了
a suspect for your hit-and-run.
- 你要释放我的客户吗? - 还不行
- You gonna let my client go? - Not yet.
拜托 他是因为任务
Come on. He's due to deploy.
还没把二等兵克里夫
Haven't brought Private Cliff in
带过来问话呢
for questioning yet.
你的四十八小时快用完了
Well, your 48-hour clock is ticking.
如果你明天还没有起诉我的客户
If you don't charge my client
你只能释放他走
by tomorrow, you have to let him go.
你知道吗 发生了一件有趣的事情
You know, a funny thing happened.
引我们去一家福尔斯彻奇的香烟商店
Sent us to a cigar store in Falls Church.
是吗?
Really?
是的 那是一个杀人案件的 犯罪现场
Yeah, it was a crime scene, a homicide.
如果你的委托人当晚
If your client wasn't driving his truck
没有开他的卡车
on base the other night,
他会不会是在福尔斯彻奇呢?
could he have been in Falls Church?
我只关心上士邓恩的权利
My only concern is Sergeant Dunne's rights.
他并没有涉嫌肇事逃逸
He wasn't involved in the hit-and-run.
不置可否
A non-denial denial.
杰森・罗巴兹 惊天大阴谋
Jason Robards, as Ben Bradlee
里面的本・布莱德里
in All the President's Men.
她没有说"不"
She didn't say "no."
哦 你疯了
Oh, you're crazy.
不 你一定需要眼镜
No, you must need glasses.
嗯 好的 回见
Yeah, yeah. All right, later.
什么事情 这么有趣?
What's so funny?
人力资源部的霍兰德
That was Hollander in HR.
说她今天早上在前门见到你
She claims that she saw you this morning
下了一辆公共汽车
at the front gate getting off a city bus.
是的 是我
Yeah, that was me.
听着 我知道我过去取笑过你
Listen, I know I made fun of you
坐公交车 但是我得承认我错了
in the past for riding the bus, but I have to admit I was wrong.
我一直在用公共交通工具
I've been using public transportation,
我也真的很喜欢
and I really like it.
- 你在耍我 - 没有
- You're kidding. - No.
我有时间读点东西
I have time to read,
打点电话 最重要的是...
make some calls and, best of all...
我可以观察人
I get to watch people.
人真的很有趣
People are fascinating.
好吧 托尼 我...
Okay, Tony, I'm...
我都弄不清我是谁了
I don't even know what I am right now.
但是我了解你 这不是你
But I know you, and this is not you.
老大 我查了上士邓恩的邮件
Boss, I went through Sergeant Dunne's e-mails,
电话记录和信用卡
phone calls and credit cards.
毫无所获
I came up empty.
他和死了的烟店店主没有丝毫联系
There's no connecting him to the dead cigar-store owner.
他有什么动机去杀那个人呢?
What would his motive be to kill the guy?
我发现邓恩和一个马里兰州的
Did find out Dunne exchanged a lot of calls
电话号码交往甚密
with a Maryland cell phone number.
是一个叫奥利维拉・钱德勒的人
Belongs to an Olivia Chandler.
好的 那就去查查她是谁
Yeah, well, find out who she is.
好的
Yup.
我们能不能冒个险 把邓恩军士的名字
Do we dare run Sergeant Dunne's name
告诉福尔斯彻奇的警察
by Falls Church PD,
看看他们能否找出点联系?
see if they can make a connection?
不能
Can't do that.
我们得保护凯莉・克拉克
Got to protect Carrie Clark.
你可以私下里去做
You can do it off the record.
负责杀人案的警官貌似认识你
The homicide detective in charge seemed to know you.
- 谁? - 哎 他带话说
- Who? - Well, he said to tell you,
"希科里之子问好"
"Hickory's son says hello."
保罗・希科里
That's Paul Dockry.
希科里 多克里 多克里
Hickory Dickory Dockry.
我和他的爸爸在军队是老相好
His dad and I were in the Corps together.
来吧 迪诺左 跟我走
Come on, DiNozzo. You're with me.
哈 人可真有趣
Huh. People are fascinating.
这个靴子印 被发现出现在海军士官
This boot print was found at a crime scene
的死亡现场
that killed a petty officer.
一样的靴子 一样的右脚跟图样
This is the same boot, the same cutout at the right heel.
你还知不知道 克里夫?
And you know what else, Cliff?
我们在后视镜上面找到了
We got your thumbprint on the rearview mirror
你的拇指纹
of that vehicle.
怎么回事?
What happened?
天很黑
It was dark.
我看到她时已经太晚了
I couldn't see her until it was too late.
你开着邓恩上士的车做什么?
What were you doing with Staff Sergeant Dunne's truck?
我喝了点小酒
I had a few drinks.
我认识一个斯坦福的女孩
I know this girl in Stafford.
在休息室 我无意中听到邓恩说
I overheard Dunne in the rec room.
他这一周过得很烂 要早点睡
Said he had a rough week and was gonna hit the rack early.
我想我可以把他的车开走 在他发现之前
Figured I'd take his truck and be back
- 就能开回来 - 胡扯!
- before he even missed it. - Bull!
你怎么知道藏着的钥匙在哪里?
How'd you know about the hidden key?
一年前 他还酗酒的时候
About a year ago, when he was still drinking,
有次他喝得烂醉 把自己锁在了车外
he got wasted, locked himself out of his truck.
他拿出藏着的钥匙 让我送他回家
Got the hidden key out, had me drive him home.
你把一个受伤的女人丢在路边送死?
You left an injured woman to die by the side of the road?
不!
No!
我停车了
I stopped.
我意识到她死了
I knew she was dead,
我才发现事情有多糟
and I realized how bad it all looked.
我喝醉了 又开着一辆偷来的车
I was drinking, I was driving a stolen vehicle.
我只是很惊慌 把车开回了停车场
I just panicked and drove back to the parking lot.
你得相信我
You got to believe me.
这是一个意外
It was an accident.
我要拘留他
I'll book him.
如果我们指控二等兵克里夫
If we charge Private Cliff
犯肇事逃逸罪
with the hit-and-run,
我们就得放邓恩上士走
we got to let Staff Sergeant Dunne go.
我没有打算这么做
I'm not ready to do that.
我们只有几个小时
We only have a few more hours
扣押邓恩
until the clock runs out on Dunne.
把他关到拘留室里去
Put him in a holding cell.
- 嘿 保罗 - 嘿 吉布斯
- Hey, Paul. - Hey, Gibbs.
抱歉 等我一下
Sorry. Just give me a sec.
我得发完这条给女儿的短信
I got to finish this text to my daughter.
这是她和我交流的唯一方式
Only way she'll communicate me.
那个孩子从不接电话
The kid never answers her phone.
都好久了
Been a long time.
你的爸爸好吗?
How's your dad?
顽固依旧
Stubborn as always.
我以为会在我的妹妹的婚礼上碰到你
Thought I might run into you at my kid sister's wedding.
哦 不 不 我不...
Oh, no, no. I'm not...
不太热衷于参加婚礼
I'm not big on weddings.
我能理解
I can understand that.
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for meeting me.
嗯 我在福尔斯彻奇碰到你的探员
Yeah. I ran into your agents in Falls Church.
我猜 那不是巧合吧
Taking it, that wasn't a coincidence.
- 呃 不是 - 所以
- Uh, no. - So,
你对我的杀人案件有何兴趣?
what's your interest in my homicide?
嗯 事情有点混乱复杂
Well, it's complicated, messy.
我们顺藤摸瓜
Following a lead.
抓住了一个指控无关的人
Holding someone on an unrelated charge.
他似乎有不在场证明
Seems to have an alibi,
但是他可能和你们死了的店主有什么联系
but he may have been involved with your dead storekeeper.
- 愿意和他一谈 - 不能谈 时机未到
- Like to talk to him. - Can't let you, not yet.
还得保护一个线人
Still trying to protect a source.
你拘留了他
You have him in custody.
是的 目前是的
Yeah, for the time being.
你的案件有什么能告诉我的?
What can you tell me about your case?
已发现沙利文是一个赌赛马的经纪人
Discovered Sullivan was a bookie.
把香烟店当做幌子
Used the cigar store as a front.
你们抓的家伙爱赌博吗?
Guy you holding like to gamble?
我会查到的
I'll find out.
谋杀案件有什么嫌疑犯吗?
You got any suspects for the murder?
有... 也没有
Yes... and no.
有超多前科的废物 温德尔・凯泽
Loser with a mile-long rap sheet, Wendell Kaiser.
参与了沙利文的好事
Into Sullivan big-time.
这个段子广为人知
Very public arguments.
凯泽甚至做出了恐吓
Kaiser even makes threats.
但是 他有无懈可击的不在场证明
However, airtight alibi.
谋杀发生时身在纽约
In New York at the time of the murder.
今早刚刚回来
Just got back this morning.
也许现在流行有不在场证明哈?
Maybe alibis are in season, huh?
好的
Okay.
吉士汉堡
Cheeseburger,
原味的 薯条
no dressing, fries.
我错过什么了吗? 你还没老啊
Did I miss something? You didn't even order.
哎 他不用是老头子的
Well, he doesn't have to.
谢谢 易兰妮
Thanks, Elaine.
你能 呃 拿来凯泽的档案吗?
Can you, uh, get me Kaiser's file?
当然
Sure.
我会把精华部分电邮给你的
I'll e-mail you the highlights.
你们抓的人 不会正好是个雇佣杀手吧?
Your guy wouldn't happen to be a hit man for hire, would he?
不 我觉得不是
No. I don't think so.
什么? 需要什么吗?
What? Need something?
是啊 一把可以切了这大块头的刀
Yeah, a knife to cut this beast.
这个可以
That'll work.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你在开玩笑
You're not serious.
她不可能嫁会给他啊
There's no way she's married to him.
快满五年了
Almost five years.
花瓶娇妻的完美诠释
The very definition of a trophy wife.
你在看什么? 奥利维拉・钱德勒
What you looking at? Olivia Chandler.
那个邓恩军士
The woman who Sergeant Dunne
互相发短信 打电话的女人
has been exchanging texts and calls with.
这个矮个的男人
That little man
一定有一个很大
must have a big,
很大的... 银行账户
big... bank account.
她嫁给他
She's married to him.
他们一起住在切维蔡斯村
They live together in Chevy Chase Village.
真会享受生活
Very la-dee-dah.
她唯一的记录是酒后驾车
Only thing on her record is a DUI.
她驾驶阿斯顿马丁左冲右突 被拘捕了
She was picked up for driving erratically in her Aston Martin.
不足为奇
So many jokes.
她开的当然是阿斯顿马丁
Of course she drives an Aston Martin.
我排查了交通摄像头
When I was searching traffic cameras
想看看是否能确定邓恩昨天晚上在谋杀案时
to see if I could place Dunne anywhere near the cigar store
出现在了雪茄店附近
the night of the murder,
找到了一些有趣的事情
I found something interesting.
奥利维拉・钱德勒的车
Olivia Chandler's car.
这是雪茄店一街区外拍摄下来的画面
Now, this was taken a block from the cigar store.
因为车窗有颜色
Because of the tinted windows,
看不出谁在里面
you can't make out who's inside.
我发给了艾比
I sent it to Abby.
希望不大 但是也许她能增强图像
It's a long shot, but maybe she can enhance the image.
沙利文是一个赌徒
Sullivan was a bookie.
福尔斯彻奇的警方锁定了一个嫌疑人
Falls Church police had a suspect,
但是他有不在场证明
but he has an alibi.
多克里探员说他会将卷宗通过邮件发过来
Detective Dockry said he was going to e-mail the file.
收到了
He did.
- 温德尔・凯泽 - 麦基
- Wendell Kaiser. - McGee
看看邓恩上士是否嗜赌成性
see if Staff Sergeant Dunne had a gambling problem
或者与这个人的任何联系
or any connection to this guy.
迪诺左...
DiNozzo...
查查奥利维拉・钱德勒
check out Olivia Chandler.
荣幸之至
With pleasure.
谢谢 老大
Thank you, boss.
需要帮忙吗?
May I help you?
希望如此
Oh, I hope so.
海军罪案调查处 特别探员安东尼・迪诺左
NCIS Special Agent Anthony DiNozzo.
海军罪案调查处?
NCIS?
我喜欢这辆车 太酷了
I love this car. It's smoking hot.
我也有意购买
I'm in the market myself.
在几款车之间摇摆不定
Between vehicles right now.
油耗很大 但是詹姆斯・邦德开的就是这款车
Terrible gas mileage, but that's what James Bond drives.
你知道吗?
Did you know that?
不知道 你有什么事情?
I have no idea. What do you want?
我们正在调查一名海军军官
Oh, we're investigating a Marine.
贾斯汀・邓恩上士
Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne.
你认识他吗?
How do you know him?
- 不认识 - 真的吗?
- I don't. - Really?
你和他经常通电话
'Cause you exchanged a lot of calls with him,
看上去你认识他
and that would suggest otherwise.
我们在戒酒会上相识
We met at an A.A. meeting.
相互交流 鼓励彼此
We talk to each other for support.
戒酒是一场持久战
Sobriety is an ongoing battle.
那你为什么说不认识他?
So why'd you say you didn't know him?
戒酒会的第二个"A"代表"匿名"
The second "A" in A.A. is for "anonymous."
我不该谈论他或其他任何人
I shouldn't be talking about him or anyone else.
我懂得
Gotcha.
你打算出趟门?
So you're taking a little trip?
我打算和好姐妹去牙买加
I'm going to Jamaica with some girlfriends.
真棒 牙买加
Yeah, mon. Jamaica.
祝你玩得开心
Well, have yourself a nice time.
你将邓恩上士与死去的赌徒
Did you connect Staff Sergeant Dunne to the dead bookie
或者福尔斯彻奇嫌疑人联系上了吗?
or the Falls Church suspect?
不 还没有
No, not yet.
根据我询问过的人的说法
Based on the people I've talked to,
看上去邓恩不是个赌徒
it appears that Dunne's not a gambler.
还有其他可以追踪的线索
I still have other avenues to pursue,
只不过没有时间完成
I just haven't had the time to do it all.
- 托尼 有发现吗? - 是的
- Tony, you got something? - Oh, yeah.
你无法想象奥利维拉・钱德勒有多正点
You won't believe how hot Olivia Chandler is.
她不上相
Photos don't do her justice.
她和邓恩上士是怎么认识的?
What's with her and Staff Sergeant Dunne?
她声称他们只在戒酒会上
Well, she claims they're only acquaintances
有泛泛之交
from A.A. meetings.
但是我认为远不止如此
But I think it's more than that.
你说你有邓恩的信用卡账单 放上来
You said you had Dunne's credit card charges-- put them up.
- 为什么? - 相信我 放到屏幕上
- Why? - Trust me, put them up there.
好了 我们要找什么?
All right, what are we looking for?
如果他们如我所想 关系亲密
Well, if they're doing what I think they're doing,
肯定不会在她家见面
they're not doing it at her place.
我认为一个来自切维蔡斯的富太太
And I don't think a rich housewife from Chevy Chase
会迈着长腿一路跑到昆迪克
is dragging those long legs all the way down to Quantico.
好的 等一下
Okay, wait. Hold on.
切维蔡斯小屋
Chevy Chase Lodge.
这里 这里和这里
There, there and there.
三个晚上 或许更多
Three nights, probably more.
记录下来 麦基
Take it down, McGee.
四十八小时时间到了
Our 48 hours are up.
是的
Yep.
什么时候能拿回我的卡车?
When do I get my truck back?
我去看看切维蔡斯小屋
I'm going to check out the Chevy Chase Lodge.
将克里夫二等兵定罪为肇事逃逸
Book Private Cliff for the hit-and-run.
一个结案 还有一个还差得远
That's one case closed, another wide open.
是的 亲爱的 我明白
Yes, dear, I understand.
真的吗?
Do you?
- 你在听吗? - 我听到了
- Do you even hear? - I hear you.
不 不 不 我... 我不会...
No, no, no. I... I would never...
... 这是你的母亲的主意吗?
Well... oh, it's your mother's idea?
是的 是我母亲的主意!
Yes, it's my mother's idea!
我为什么不感到惊讶呢?
Why does that not surprise me?
我得挂了 有位客人等着我呢
I have to go. I have a guest waiting.
真的有客人在等着我
I do have a guest waiting.
我没有胡说
I'm not making that up.
... 你能帮帮我吗 先生?
Uh... could you help me, please, sir?
这是谁? 喂?
Who is that? Hello?
好的 我等会儿再打给你
Okay. I'll call you later.
- 好吧! - 我才不会打呢
- Fine! - Like hell I will.
你结婚了吗?
You married?
没有...
Oh. No. Uh...
我是联邦探员
I'm a federal agent.
迪诺左
DiNozzo.
想问你几个问题
Like to ask a few questions.
好吧 联邦探员 问吧
All right, federal agent, ask away.
你见过这个人吗?
Have you seen this man?
见过
Yeah.
是的 见过
Yeah, sure.
算是常客了
Sort of a regular.
他是一个人来还是...?
So, does he come alone or...?
他想让我这么想
Well, he'd like me to think that.
不 他的朋友从不来大厅
No, his friend never comes to the lobby.
他停车 她直接去房间
He parks the car, and she goes directly to the room.
你会想 一个人或者俩人都结婚了 对吧?
So you got to figure, you know, one or both are married, right?
没错
Right. Yeah.
所以你从未见过她?
So you've never seen her?
事实上 我曾经
Well, actually, I did the old
敲错过一次门
knock-on-the-wrong-door routine one time.
她长得像这样?
She look like this?
是的 就是她
Yeah, that's her.
像这样的女人 你不会忘记
Woman like that, you do not forget.
对吧? 你能想象一晚上和...
Right? I mean, can you imagine what one night with...
我发誓 这个老女人是一个疯子
I swear, the old witch is psychic.
如果我对另一个女人有这么多幻想...
If I have so much as a thought of another woman...
你不必接通它
You don't have to answer that.
我必须要接 你...?!
I have to. What...?!
...有什么事情?
...do you want?
知道了 祝你好运
I got it. Good luck.
等等 你需要... 如果...
Just, do you need... if...
拿张名片吧 先生
Take a card, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
给你
Here.
我喜欢和你喝酒 达克
Ah, always enjoy having a drink with you, Duck,
但是你不会听完交响乐绕路来这里
but this isn't exactly on your way home from the symphony.
你想说什么?
What's on your mind?
出于好奇 我正打算问你
Well, curiously, I was about to ask you that.
你看起来... 心事重重
You've seemed... troubled
自从你昨天尸检时接了那通电话
since you took that call in Autopsy yesterday.
通常你很擅长隐藏自己的感情
Usually you're a master at hiding your feelings.
你的职业建议是?
That your professional opinion?
和一名心理侧写师
The occupational hazard
工作的职业风险
of working with a profiler.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
有点担心凯莉・克拉克
A little concerned about Carrie Clark.
- 那名律师? - 是的 她很出色
- The lawyer? - Yeah, she's good.
她让当事人被无罪释放
She got her client released without being charged.
可是呢...?
I sense a "but."
恩 她不至于毫无良心可言
Well, she does have a conscience.
这是一件好事 对吧?
Well, that's a good thing, isn't it?
她可能有意或无意
We learned some things about her client
引导我们去了解她客户的信息
that she may or may not have led us to.
是一些特殊信息吗?
Privileged information?
达克 这件事情我得万分小心
Doc, I got to be careful how I handle this.
我得为凯莉着想
For Carrie's sake.
弄不好她会因此吊销执照的
She could get disbarred.
杰斯罗 我太了解你了
Well, I know you, Jethro.
你总是为别人着想 总以为自己是对的
It sounds as if she's doing the right thing, as you are.
音乐会如何?
So how was the concert?
柴可夫斯基第钢二琴协奏曲 演奏得极好
Great. Tchaikovsky's Second.
原来他为电影作过曲 这我还是第一次知道
I never realized that he wrote music for the movies.
这辆车我想要好久了
That's a car I've always had the hots for.
我真该买一辆的
Maybe that's what I should get.
都是老爷车
It's too old.
你怎么开啊
You can't drive a car like that.
太不切实际了
It's not practical.
麦基 你这个人就这毛病
That's the problem with you, McGeezer.
什么都要切合实际
Everything has to be practical.
其实...
What...
我想说 从来没见你
What I mean is, I've never known you
冒过哪怕一丝一毫的险
to do anything even a little risqué.
托尼 你不了解我的私生活 请不要乱说
Tony, you have no idea what I do on my time off.
是的 我是不了解
You know, that's true, I don't.
那你说说也无妨?
Why don't you tell me?
有分享 有惊喜 有感动
Share. Rock me. Sock me.
目标人物温德尔・凯泽出现
Well, there's Wendell Kaiser.
你说福尔斯彻奇警局是不是也在查他呢?
Wonder if Falls Church PD is tailing him, too.
凯泽是他们的嫌犯
Kaiser's their suspect.
他去做礼拜吗?
Is Kaiser going to church?
不是 例会而已
No. It's an A.A. meeting.
他们每天早上都会在这里集会
They meet here every morning at this time.
嗯? 你怎么知道?
Wait, how do you know that?
安东尼!
Anthony!
你来这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
你不是应该今晚才来吗?
Your meeting's not until tonight.
米勒教士 我... 是来...
Reverend Miller, I, uh...
有新人要加入吗?
Bringing a new member?
这个...
Um...
他还在考虑这件事情 他对枪声有点儿阴影
He's thinking about it. A little gun-shy.
麦基 这是教士
McGee, the Rev.
加入我们吧
Please join us.
安全有保障
It's a very safe place.
我们欢迎任何人的加入
All are welcome.
托尼 这是怎么回事?
Tony, what's going on?
你在戒酒吗?
Do you have a drinking problem?
那倒没有...
No. No, I just...
我就是加入了他们的资助团体而已
I joined this men's support group.
每周花两个晚上在教堂大厅见面
Meets in the church hall two nights a week.
真的吗?
You serious?
是啊
Mm-hmm.
我懂...
I know, it...
这一点儿不像我的作风 可是...
it doesn't sound like me, but...
去年发生那么多事以后... 我
with the past year, I just...
想换换环境
wanted to shake things up a little bit.
认识一些新朋友
Meet some new people.
在健身馆有人给我提起这个组织
This guy at the gym told me about the group,
我觉得这个主意不错
and I thought it sounded like a good idea.
而且... 这里... 挺有趣的
And it... it is, it's fun.
教士有天早上开车带我去了昆迪克
The Rev drove me to Quantico the other morning.
他这人很有意思
Interesting guy.
他教我如何少去评判别人
He's helping me be less judgmental.
告诉你啊 凯泽要在这儿呆上好一阵子呢
You know, Kaiser's going to be here for a while.
我们先回去吧
We should get back.
邓恩上士 奥利维拉・钱德勒
Sergeant Dunne, Olivia Chandler
还有温德尔・凯泽
and Wendell Kaiser
他们三人都有一个共同点
all have one thing in common.
那就是 他们都去那个一对一集会
They all go to A.A. meetings.
可能他们就是在那里认识的吧?
That's probably where they met.
上士和这位花瓶妻是恋人关系
The sergeant and the trophy wife are lovers.
切维蔡斯旅馆的前台职员
The desk clerk at the Chevy Chase Lodge
说他们是店里的常客
said that they were regulars.
就像电影 体热 里面演的一样
It's just like that movie Body Heat.
威廉・赫特和 凯瑟琳・特纳主演的哦
William Hurt and Kathleen Turner.
啊 这个女人太迷人了
God, she was really something, boss.
让人为之癫狂
A head turner.
好吧 说跑题了
But I digress.
总而言之他们和这对恋人一样 年轻气盛
Anyway, they were young lovers, just like these two,
都想打富老公的主意 谋他的财
and they wanted the rich husband's money
害他的命
and him out of the way.
另一方面
On the other hand, you've got
温德尔・凯泽赌债缠身
Wendell Kaiser, who's deep in debt to his bookie
也想杀了债主一了百了
and needs him off his back.
所以他们互相借刀杀人 为对方解决问题
So they help each other out and switch murders.
当凯泽在纽约的时候
While Kaiser was in New York,
邓恩和奥利维拉一起合伙杀了他的债主
Dunne killed the bookie with Olivia's help.
她开车载他 她自己的车就在附近
She drove him. Her car was in the vicinity.
没有人会去怀疑他们?
Who would ever suspect them?
既没有联系 也没有动机
I mean, there's no connection, no motive.
明天邓恩上士要接受派遣去别处
Tomorrow Sergeant Dunne is going to deploy
而奥利维拉・钱德勒要出国去牙买加
and Olivia Chandler is off to Jamaica.
我猜他们离开以后
And I'm betting that while they're away,
她的丈夫会出严重车祸
her husband's going to have a terrible accident
这一切都是拜凯泽所赐
at the hands of Mr. Kaiser here,
而他们之间一点儿关系都没有
a man with whom he has no connection.
两起谋杀案 而这三个人却都有不在场证明
Two murders, three solid alibis.
这个想法挺有意思
Interesting theory.
我们知道这项指控证明起来十分困难
We know it's going to be a hard conspiracy for us to prove.
要万事小心 毕竟这不是我们的案件
We got to be careful-- it's not our case.
我有办法
There's a way.
找到最弱的那环就行
Find the weak link.
嘿 凯泽
Hey, Kaiser.
你有空吗?
You got a minute?
多克里探长
Detective Dockry.
我们的问题不是解决了吗?
I thought we were done.
沙利文的情况 我都告诉你了
Look, I told you everything I know about Sullivan.
没错 但是出了一点儿小问题
Yeah, well, something's come up.
跟我去局里吧 我们来谈谈
Let's go to the station. We can talk about it.
不了 这里就挺好
Nah, I'm not going anywhere.
听我说 我和沙利文的死一点关系都没有
Look, I had nothing to do with Sullivan's murder.
我当时在纽约 你查过的
I was in New York, man. You checked it out.
你非得逼我在你的朋友面前下手吗?
You really want to do this in front of your friends?
我不想跟你离开这里
I'm not going anywhere with you.
你的同伙邓恩上士和她的女友的事情
We know about your buddy, Sergeant Dunne,
我们已经知道了
and his girlfriend.
现在我说了算
So let me explain how this works.
你要是第一个招供 就有机会和我们谈条件
First suspect to flip on the others gets the deal.
奥利维拉・钱德勒
Olivia Chandler?
嘿 老吉
Hey, Gibbs.
迪诺左说要是你不在家
DiNozzo told me that if you weren't at home
就来这里找你
I would probably find you here.
请坐
Have a seat.
有什么事情吗?
There a problem?
没有 我...
No, I...
我刚听说福尔斯彻奇警局
just heard that Falls Church PD
逮捕了我之前的委托人邓恩上士
arrested my former client, Sergeant Dunne.
是吗?
Really?
是的 他们以多项罪名起诉他
Yeah, they booked him on multiple charges,
说他预谋杀人 并杀害他人
including conspiracy to commit murder and murder one.
他们怎么抓到他的?
How'd they get him?
他的同伙之一
Apparently one of his coconspirators
上交了证物
turned state's evidence.
有时候好运来了... 挡也挡不住
Sometimes... you get lucky.
真是这样吗?
Mmm, is that what it was?
他们拿到搜查令 在邓恩家
They got a warrant and cinched the case against Dunne
马桶水箱里找到了凶器 是一把刀
when they found the murder weapon, a knife,
于是定了他的罪
in his bathroom toilet tank.
真不错
That's great.
你还好吗?
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
找不到不好的理由? 我做了分内之事
Why wouldn't I be? I did my job.
让他免于肇事逃逸的责罚
I got Dunne off on the hit-and-run.
是的 你办得很好
Yeah, you did it well.
那以后 他无论发生什么
Yes, and whatever happened to him after that,
都与我无关
it's not my concern.
天网恢恢 疏而不漏
Justice was served, all around.
好的 请用餐
Okay. Here you go.
要一起吃晚餐吗?
Care to join me for dinner?
肉馅糕配土豆泥 真不错
Hmm, meat loaf and mashed potatoes?
我最喜欢吃这些 我很愿意和你共享晚餐
My favorite. I would be happy to.
马上就好
Coming right up.
易兰妮 谢谢你
Thanks, Elaine.
看来我们还是有一些共同点的
I think that you and me have a few things in common.